Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - F
    - Forsyth, Ilene, History of Art, 1984, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Forsyth, John D., Medical Center, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Forsythe, Edwin J., Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Forsythe, George H. Jr., Fine Arts, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Fortuna, Michael, Office of Management Education, 1973, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Foster, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Foster, Morris, Zoology, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Foster, Veo G., Natural Science, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Foulke, James A., Industrial Engineering, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Foust, Alan S., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1951 (Box 5)
      (na 471)
    - Fowler, Harold, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Fox, Kenneth, Physics, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Fox, Robert S., Education, 1950, 1956, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Foyle, William R., Business Administration, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Fralick, F. Bruce, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Francis, Thomas, Jr., Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Francke, Don E., University Hospital, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Franken, Peter A., Physics, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Frankena, William K., Philosophy, 1956, 1964, 1978 (Box 5)
      (na 476)
    - Franz, Norman, Wood Technology, 1964, 1954 (Box 5)
      (na 477)
    - Fraser, Celeste (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 5)
    - Fraser, Roderick, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Frederick, Julian, Mechanical Engineering, 1973, 1959, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Frederickson, Barbara, Psychology, Women's Studies, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Freedman, David, Biblican Studies, 1977, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Freedman, Ronald, Sociology; Population Studies Center, 1963, 1956, 1974 (Box 5)
      (na 478, na 492)
    - Freehling, William, History, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Freeman, James W., Metallurgical Engineering, 1964, 1960 (Box 5)
      (nb 285)
    - French, Arthur B., Internal Medicine (Box 5)
    - French, David G., Social Work, 1958 (Box 5)
    - French, David M., Dean, Flint, 1967 (Box 5)
    - French, Esther L., Physical Education for Women, 1962, 1971 (Box 5)
    - French, Joyce, ISR, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Frenza, James P., Community Relations, 1976, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Freud, Clarice, Social Work, 1955, 1965, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Freudenberg, Jim, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Frey, Charles, Surgery, 1964, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Frey, William, Center for Population Planning, 1993, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Fricke, Benno G., Bureau of Psychological Services; Psychology, 1957, 1963 (Box 5)
      (na 487)
    - Fricke, Cedric V., Finance, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Fried, Mike, ISR, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Frieder, William, Basketball, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Friedman, Robert S., Political Science; Institute of Public Administration, 1963, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Fries, Charles C., English, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Fritz, Elmer, 1953, 1952 (Box 5)
    - Fritz, Irving B., Physiology, 1959, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Fritz, Ralph, Symphony, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Froseth, James, Music, 1984, 1991, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Frost, Carolyn, Library, 1989, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Frost, Marion, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Frost, Renee, Office of Administrative Systems, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Frost, Robert, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Frye, Billy E., Zoology; VP for Academic Affairs, 1966, 1980, 1983, 1978, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Frye, Linda, Alumni Association, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Fujii, Henry, University Press, 1956 (Box 5)
      (na 494)
    - Fuller, Elsie R., Housing; Dean of Women, 1959, 1952 (Box 5)
      (na 495)
    - Furstenberg, A. C. (SEE: Rural Health Conference), 1952 (Box 5)
    - Fusfeld, Daniel R., Economics, 1961, 1969 (Box 5)
  - G
    - Gaa, Charles L., Business Administration, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Gable, Tom, Public Health, 1970, 1963, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Gable, Tom Mrs., Public Health, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Gable, William, Political Science; Institute of Public Administration, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Gage, James A., Industrial Engineering, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Gage, Lois, Nursing, 1985, 1996, 1989, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Gainsley, Rolland, Security, 1966, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Gaiss, Aloysius, German, 1955 (Box 5)
    - Galbreath, Robert, Civil Engineering, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Gallagher, Tanya M., Speeching and Hearing Science, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Galler, Bernard, LSA; Computer Science, 1978, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Galliher, Herbert, Industrial Engineering, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Gallups, William C., Accounting, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Gamson, Sociology, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Gannon, John J., Public Health Engineering; Environmental and Industrial Health, 1963, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Gantt, John G., Photo Duplication Service, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Garbaty, Thomas J., English Language and Literature, 1966, 1982, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Garbutt, Jack A., Drawing and Painting (Box 5)
      (na 503)
    - Gardner, Wallce W., Business Administration, 1954 (Box 5)
    - Garner, Harvey L., Electrical Engineering, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Garnish, Naval Science, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Garrison, Garnet R., Broadcasting Service; Speech, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Gary, Gordon J., Engineering, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Gaudi, Arthur, Law; History, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Gault, Edgar, Marketing, 1966, 1951, 1959 (Box 5)
      (na 504, nb 293)
    - Gay, Helen, Zoology, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Gaylord, Alan T., English, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Gehner, Martin, Architecture, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Gehring, Frederick, Mathematics, 1994, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Geis, George L., CRLT; Psych. And Res. Assoc., 1970 (Box 5)
    - Geleerloos, Oren, Biology, Dearborn campus, 1970 (Box 5)
    - George, B. James Jr., Law, 1964, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Georgopoulos, Basil S., Survey Research Center, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Gerard, Ralph W., Neurophysiology, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Gere, Anne Ruggles, Education; English, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Gerhardt, Philipp, Microbiology, 1953, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Gerhart, Paul, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Gerrish, Howard, Education, 1954 (Box 5)
    - Gershowitz, Henry, Medical School, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Gessner, Quentin, Extension Service, 1974, 1971, 1970, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Getting, Vlado A., Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Ghitalla, Armando, Music, 1979, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Ghosh, S. N., 1968 (Box 5)
    - Gibalda, Ronald, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Gies, George, Center for Learning and Teaching, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Gies, Thomas G., Finance, 1970, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Giever, Paul, Industrial health, 1963, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Gifford, Duane H., University Relations, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Gikas, Paul, Pathology, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Gilbert, Elmer G., Aeronautical Engineering, 1959, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Gilbert, George, Power house, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Gilbert, Lawrence I., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Gilchrist, Brian E., Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Giles, Sidney, Business Office, 1956 (Box 5)
    - Gilgenbach, Ronald M., Nuclear Engineering, 1981, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Gill, Gerald C., Meterology, 1968, 1971, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Gilliland, Gail (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 5)
    - Gilmour, Joyce, English Language Institute, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Gilsdorf, William O., Bureau of School Services, 1961, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Gindin, James J., English, 1960, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Gingles, Carle, Dentistry, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Gingras, Fran, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Ginopolis, Jane, Social Work, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Ginsburg, Elliot K., Near Eastern Studies, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Girten, Naval Science, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Gitelman, Zvi Y, Political Science; Center for Russian and East European Studies, 1991, 1987, 1981, 1978, 1972, 1969, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Gjelsness, Rudolph, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Glaser, Donald A., Physics, 1955 (Box 5)
    - Glasgow, Robert, Music, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Glass, David R., UMRI, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Glasser, Paul H., Social Work, 1960, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Gleason, Grand Rapids Extension Service, 1955 (Box 5)
    - Glick, Edward, WUOM; Symphony, 1956 (Box 5)
    - Glicksberg, Daniel H., English Language Institute, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Glysson, Eugene, Civil Engineering, 1987, 1980, 1973, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Gochman, David, Public Health Administration, 1971, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Goddard, Joe D., Chemical Engineering, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Goebel, Paul, Regent, 1967, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Goetz, Robert O., Civil Engineering, 1960, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Gold, Martin, Psychology; IST, 1979, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Goldberg, Daniel, Men's tennis (Box 5)
    - Goldberg, David, Population Studies Center; Sociology; Institute of Public Administration, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Goldberg, Jack L., Mathematics, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Goldberg, Leo, Astronomy, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Goldenberg, Edie, LSA, 1996, 1990, 1989, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Goldman, Alvin, Philosophy, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Goldman, Joseph, Music, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Goldman, Rachel, Engineering, 1999 (Box 5)
    - Goldstein, Laurence, English, 1995 (Box 5)
    - Gomberg, Henry, Electrical Engineering, 1952, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Gomez, Luis O., Far Eastern Languages and Literature, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Gooch, Donald B., Design, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Good, Charles W., 1954 (Box 5)
      (na 521)
    - Good, Warren, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Goodall, Leonard E., Chancellor - Dearborn campus; Political Science, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Goode, Harry H., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Gooding, Robert (Box 5)
    - Goodman, Barbara, IST, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Goodman, Frederick L., SACUA, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Goodman, George, School of Business?, 1973, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Goodman, Judith, Business Administration, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Goodman, Truzella, Housing E.O.M., 1989 (Box 5)
    - Goodwin, Bill, Development Office, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Goodwin, Ernest S. L., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Gordon, Jesse E., Psychology, 1960, 1975, 1964 (Box 5)
      (nb 307)
    - Gordon, Kenneth F., Chemical Engineering, 1959 (Box 5)
      (nb 309)
    - Gordon, Roger, Economics, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Gordus, Adon, Chemistry, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Gordy, Charles B., Industrial Engineering, 1961 (Box 5)
      (nb 310)
    - Gore, George J., Industrial Management, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Gores, Walter W. J., Design, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Gorla, Gina, Law, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Gosling, Glenn D., University Press (Box 5)
    - Gosling, John R. G., Obstetrics and Gynocology, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Gosling, L. A. Peter, Geography, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Gosling, William, Library, 1996, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Goss, Thomas, Athletics (Box 5)
    - Gottesman, Leonard E., Psychology; Institute of Gerontology, 1969 (Box 5)
    - Gottschalk, Earl C., Jr., Journalism, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Goulding, Herbert J., Mechanism and Engineering Drawing (Box 5)
    - Grabar, Oleg, Fine Arts Dept., 1958 (Box 5)
    - Grace, Frank, Political Science, 1961, 1958 (Box 5)
      (na 524)
    - Graebel, William P., Applied Mechanics, 1960, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Graefen, William, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Graf, Otto, German, 1955, 1964 (Box 5)
      (na 525)
    - Graff, Lou, 1953, 1954, 1955 (Box 5)
      (na 526-na 527)
    - Graham, Bruce D., Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1954 (Box 5)
      (nb 313)
    - Graham, Samuel A., Natural Sciences, 1953, 1962 (Box 5)
      (na 528)
    - Graham, Stanley, Publications Office, 1970 (Box 5)
      (nb 314)
    - Grambeau, Rodney J., Physical Education (Box 5)
    - Gramen, Robert, Business Administration, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Gramlich, Ned, IPPS, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Granoff, Michael H., Accounting, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Grassmuck, George, Political Science, 1981, 1973, 1963, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Graves, Harvey W., Nuclear Engineering, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Graves, Helen, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Graves, Luther J., Jr., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Graves, William H., Automotive Engineering, 1958, 1956 (Box 5)
      (na 530)
    - Gray, Asa, Natural History (Box 5)
      (na 531)
    - Gray, Donald, Civil Engineering, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Gray, Whitmore, Law, 1963, 1960, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Green, Bert I., ISR, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Green, Elizabeth A. H., Music, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Green, Robert, Medical School, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Green, Vivian, State & Community Relations, 1981, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Greenbaum, Leonard, Phoenix Project, 1973, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Greenberg, Leo, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Greenberg, Marshall G., Psychology, 1961 (Box 5)
      (nb 318)
    - Greene, Katherine, 1951 (Box 5)
      (na 534)
    - Greenhutt, Morris, English, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Greenman, Emerson F., Museum of Anthropology; Anthropology, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Greenquist, Peter, WUOM, 1981, 1976, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Greenshields, Bruce D., Civil Engineering; Transportation Institute, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Greenvield, Richard, University Club of Ann Arbor, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Greenwald, Dorothy, Written Communication, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Greenwood, Donald, Aerospace Engineering, 1971, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Greer, Frances, Music, 1955, 1958, 1961 (Box 5)
      (na 538-na 542, nb 320)
    - Greey, George, Physical Education, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Gregerson, Linda, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Gregory, G. Robinson, Natural Resources, 1959 (Box 5)
      (na 543)
    - Greig, Walter, Cleary College, Ypsilanti, 1954 (Box 5)
      (na 536)
    - Grennau, John, Foundry Practice, 1961 (Box 5)
      (na 544)
    - Greve, J. Herman (Box 5)
      (na 554)
    - Grew, Raymond, History, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Grew, Raymond, History, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Griffin, Clare, Business Administration, 1949, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Griffin, James B., Archaeology; Anthropology; Museum of Anthropology, 1950, 1960, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Griffith, John R., Hospital Administration, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Grigaut, Paul, History of Art, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Grimes, Dale M., Electrical Engineering, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Grimes, Don, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Grimshaw, Thomas, Administration Services, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Grizzle, Jessy, Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1991, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Groat, Linda, Architecture, 1996, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Groesbeck, Byron L., Admissions, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Groesbeck, Edward G., Office of Registration and Records, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Grossman, Robert, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Grosz, Donald D., Music, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Grote, Steve (Box 5)
    - Grotrian (Grotian), Harvey, Office of Financial Aid, 1986, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Grove, Nancy, Bureau of Appointments, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Grubb, Rosemary, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Grzesnikwoski, Edwin, Music, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Gulari, Erdogan, Chemical Engineering, 1986, 1978, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Gupta, English, 1955 (Box 5)
      (na 564)
    - Gurin, Gerald, Survey Research Center; Institute for Social Research, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Gurin, Patricia Y., Psychology, 1981, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Gurnis, Mike, Geology, 1993, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Gustafson, Felix G., Botany, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Guthe, Karl F., Zoology, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Gutmann, David, Psychology, 1973, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Guttmacher, Alan F., Planned Parenthood, World Population (Box 5)
    - Guttman, Louis, Sociology; Psychology, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Gwin, John, 1950 (Box 5)
      (na 567)
    - Gyorey, Geza L., Nuclear Engineering, 1960 (Box 5)
  - H
    - Haas, Rosamond, News Service, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Haase, Caroline, Institute of Continuing Legal Education, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Haber, William, Economics, 1973, 1960, 1950, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Hacker, Herbert, Jr., Electrical Engineering, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Hacker, Sylvia S., Nursing, 1981 (Box 5)
    - Hackett, Arthur, Voice (Box 5)
    - Haddad, George I., Electrical Engineering, 1960, 1973, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Hadden, Richard, University Press, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Hadden-Ellis, Marise (Box 5)
    - Haddock, Fred T., Astronomy; Electrical Engineering, 1958, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Haefner, Don P., Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Hagar, John, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Hagen, John W., Psychology; Center for Human Growth and Development, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Hagopian, John V., English (Box 5)
      (na 657)
    - Hahn, Harlan, Political Science, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Haight, Cameron, Surgery, 1961, 1968 (Box 5)
      (na 609)
    - Hainsworth (Box 5)
    - Hairston, Nelson G., Zoology, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Hakken, Howard, University Architect (Box 5)
    - Halford, Joseph O., 1949 (Box 5)
    - Hall, Charles ? (Box 5)
    - Hall, Clifton, German, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Hall, Donald, English, 1964, 1962, 1975 (Box 5)
      (na 672)
    - Hall, Donna, Natural Resources, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Hall, George, Higher Education, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Hall, Gilbert O., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Hall, John, Civil Engineering, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Hall, John, Center for Japanese Studies; History (Box 5)
      (na 610)
    - Hall, John R., Jr. (Box 5)
    - Hall, Keith W., Mechanical Engineering, 1954, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Hall, Phillippe, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Hall, Robert B., Geography, 1962, 1952 (Box 5)
      (na 673)
    - Hall, William, Business, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Halladay, Lloyd, English Language Institute, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Halloran, Dan, Housing, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Halloran, John H., Education, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Halmos, Paul R., Mathematics, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Halpern, Edward, Mathematics, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Halpern, Jean, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Halstead, Margo, Music, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Halstead, William P., Speech Communication and Theatre, 1980, 1952 (Box 5)
    - Hamilton, Jack, University Relations, 1965, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Hamilton, John, Publications, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Hamilton, Louif, Nuclear Engineering, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Hamm, Kathleen, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Hammett, Ralph, Architecture, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Hammitt, Frederick G., Mechanical and Nuclear Engineering, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Hampton, Lee, Information Services, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Hampton, William, News Service, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Hamson, Charles John, Law, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Hamson, Edwin M., Romance Languages, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Hancock, Walton M., Industrial Engineering, 1963, 1975 (Box 5)
    - Handler, A. B., Planning, 1969, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Handler, Wallace M. (Box 5)
      (na 614)
    - Hanlon, Philip, Mathematics, 1987, 1991 (Box 5)
    - Hann, Arthur S., Business Administration, 1960, 1953, 1969 (Box 5)
      (na 674)
    - Hannum, William H., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Hansen, Arthur G., Mechanical Engineering, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Hansen, Helene (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 5)
    - Hansen, Holger M., Engineering Mechanics, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Hansen, Will, Civil Engineering, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Hanson, H. H., Music, 1973 (Box 5)
    - Hanson, Philip, Bureau of School Services, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Hanson, Robert D., Civil Engineering, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Hanson, Russell G., International Center, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Harburg, Ernest, Psych. And Epid., 1963 (Box 5)
    - Harden, Elaine, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Hardman, Harold F., Pharmacology, 1958 (Box 5)
      (na 617)
    - Hardy, Kenneth R., Civil Engineering, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Harger, Harold, Assistant to the Dean, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Harold, John Downs, Extension Services, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Harper, Paul (Box 5)
    - Harper, Royster, Dean, 1991, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Harrell, E. Richard, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Harrington, James B., Engineering Mechanics, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Harris, Milton, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Harris, Norman C., Education, 1961, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Harris, Patricia Roberts, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Priscilla J., University Relations, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Randy, VP of Finance, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Robert B., Civil Engineering, 1960, 1983, 1978, 1970, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Robert E., Housing E.O.M., 1987 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Robert J., Law, 1959, 1969, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Ruth, Physical Education, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Harris, Thomas A., Military Science, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Harrison, Don K., Education, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Harrison, George B., English, 1960, 1950 (Box 6)
      (na 677a)
    - Harrison, Michael, Electrical Engineering, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Harrison, Saul, Psychiatry, 1975, 1956 (Box 6)
    - Harrison, T. R., 1972 (Box 6)
    - Harrison, Timothy, Surgery, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Harrison, Walter, University Relations, 1996, 1989, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Hart, S. V., 1953, 1951 (Box 6)
      (na 616, na 618)
    - Hartford, Maureen, Vice President for Student Affairs, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Hartman, Francis, Extension Service, 1955, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Hartwig, Marie, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Harvey, William B., Law, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Harwith, Ronald, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Hasking, Lyle, WUOM, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Haslanger, Sally, Philosophy/Women's Studies, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Hatcher, Harlan, 1954, 1966, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Hauenstein, Nelson, Music, 1955, 1960, 1971 (Box 6)
      (na 683)
    - Haugh, Harold A., Music, 1956, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Haugh, Robert, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Hauser, Norbert, Industrial Engineering, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Hausser, Doris, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Havelock, Ronald G., ISR, 1973, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Havlick, Spensor, Natural Resources, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Hawkins, Carl, Law School, 1957, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Hawley, Amos H., Sociology, 1958 (Box 6)
    - Hawley, Arthur, Geography, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Hawley, Ransom S., Mechanical Engineering, 1950, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Hawthorne, Victor M., Epidemiology, 1995 (Box 6)
    - Hay, George E., Mathematics, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Hayden, G. Sutherland, Bureau of School Services; Education, 1961, 1967, 1972, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Hayes, Douglas, School of Business Administration, 1965, 1972, 1952, 1956 (Box 6)
      (na 685)
    - Hayes, Edward, Compensation Plans and Personnel Info Systems, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Hayes, Helen, University Professional Theater, 1962 (Box 6)
      (na 623)
    - Hayes, John P., EECS, 1999, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Hayes, John T., Surgery, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Hayes, Kim, Engineering, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Hayes, Samuel P., Economics, 1961, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Hayner, C. Irene, Library Science, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hayner, Norman, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Haynes, Harley A. (Box 6)
    - Hays, William, Psychology, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Haythornthwaite, Robert M., Engineering Science, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hazen, Wayne E., Physics, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Hazzard, Albert S., 1955 (Box 6)
      (na 624)
    - Hazzard, James S., Naval Science, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Heady, C. Ferrel, Political Science, 1950, 1961 (Box 6)
      (na 686)
    - Healy, Dean, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Healy, Mrs., 1954 (Box 6)
      (na 625)
    - Heath, Edward C., Medical School, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Heath, Eva, Housing E.O.M., 1987 (Box 6)
    - Heath-Stubbs, John F. A., English, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Heatley, Leo J., Safety, 1979 (Box 6)
    - Hebert, 1947 (Box 6)
    - Hedrich, Walter A., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Heers, Wendel W., Art, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hefner, Robert A., Jr., Psychology, 1969, 1968, 1959, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Heger, Theodore, Music, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Heglar, Roger, Anthropology, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Heimbach, Clinton L., Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Heinrick, E. William, Minerology, 1956 (Box 6)
    - Heller, Catherine, 1952 (Box 6)
    - Heller, Donald, Education, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Heller, Irene, Education, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Hellerich, Mahlon, Education, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Hellwarth, Arlen R., Engineering, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Hellworth, George, Research Administration, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Helmers, Hendrik, Business Administration, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Helms, William, Physical Education, 1966 (Box 6)
    - Hempel, George H., Business Administration, 1962, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Henderson, Algo, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Henderson, John Woodworth, Opthalmology, 1968, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Hendricksen, Daniel P., English Language Institute, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Henion, Col., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Henkin, Alexander, Mechanical Engineering, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Henle, Paul, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Hennessy, Albert, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Henninger, Ann, Physiology, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Henry, Edwin, Electrical Engineering, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Hensley, William, News Service, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Hepler, Harold, Naval Science, 1964 (Box 6)